

Marcus Vinicius

Date of birth: 28 Mar 1995

Nationality: Brazilian

My Website / Portfolio

Link: https://marcus-portfolio-lac.vercel.app/

CONTACT Porto, Portugal (Home)





marcus.relation@gmail.com



(+351) 912981585



912981585 (WhatsApp)

ABOUT ME

Full Stack Web Developer | Front-end Developer | UI/UX Designer

As a Full Stack Web Developer with a focus on frontend. I specialize in modern technologies and frameworks, including JavaScript, TypeScript, and have extensive experience with React.js, Next.js, SASS, Styled-components, Tailwind.css. Backend with Node.js, Express.js and MongoDB.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2023 - CURRENT Lisboa

Creative Developer - Frondend Innovagency

2022 - 2023 Penafiel, Portugal

Full Stack Developer Anca Design Studio

2021 - 2022 Porto, Portugal

Full Stack Developer WMC Publicidade

2019 - 2020 São Paulo, Brazil

UX e UI Designer byBnD Informática

2016 - 2018 São Paulo, Brazil

Web Designer Grupo Solví

2016 - 2016 São Paulo, Brazil

Web Designer Essencis Soluções Ambientais

2014 – 2016 São Paulo, Brazil

Graphic Designer Impacto Eletronics

2013 – 2014 São Paulo, Brazil

Graphics designer RM Comunicação Visual

Graphic design

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

current - Bachelor Degree - Systems analysis and development

FIAP

https://www.fiap.com.br

Full Stack Web Development

EDIT School

https://weareedit.io/

Bachelor Degree - Advertising and Social Communication

FAPCOM - Faculdade Paulus de Comunicação

https://www.fapcom.edu.br/

Front-end Development - Rocketseat

https://www.rocketseat.com.br/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S):

Portuguese Other language(s):

English Spanish

B2 B2

Writing B2 Writing B2

UI/UX Designer

MERN Stack (MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS, NodeJS)

Sistemas de Gestão de Conteúdo (CMS):Wordpress, Shopify, StoryBlok